This is Dating Horror
Story, Episode 8. So
I matched with this
girl on Tinder. Absolutely
gorgeous, investment girl boss
energy, the kind that
makes you think she's
definitely out of my
league. We talked for
a week. Tinder, then
Instagram. She was funny,
interesting, easy to talk
to. Everything seemed perfect.
We agreed to meet
at a coffee shop.
The first 10 minutes?
Great. We were vibing.
I was feeling confident.
I got up to
grab a coffee, asked
if she wanted one.
She said no thanks.
I come back to
the table. There's a
third person sitting there
now. A girl I've
never seen. Oh, this
is my business partner.
Her business partner immediately
starts asking about my
income, my job, my
studies. Then, what if
you could be making
an extra thousand dollars
a month? And she
lays out this business
model. You recruit three
people. Those three people
recruit three more people.
Each person earns a
cut of everything everyone
below them sells. I
look at my date.
My date is smiling
at me. I said,
And this was genuine.
So this is like
a pyramid scheme, right?
This ain't no date?
My date goes, No,
no, no, it's not
a pyramid scheme. It's
an MLM company. Totally
different. I said, Oh
man, I totally forgot
my dog has a
vet appointment. I grabbed
my coffee and walked
out. I laughed so
hard on the drive
home, I had to
pull over. My dog
doesn't have a vet
appointment. My dog is
fine.