So I was stationed
in South Korea, early
20s, army private. One
night, this tall redhead
guy asks me to
dinner. My friend warns
me it's a bad
idea but won't say
why. I said, what's
the worst that could
happen? I get a
free meal and we
don't click? As you
may have guessed, that
was not the worst
that could happen. First
he's late. Then he
calls asking if I
have cash for the
taxi. Great start. We
get in a Korean
taxi. I ask what
he thinks of Korea
so far. He goes
off on a rant
about how, these people
don't even speak English.
A kid runs into
the street to grab
a ball, and he
starts yelling about how,
these people have no
common sense. I tell
him we're in their
country, not the other
way around. He gets
mad, puts his headphones
on, and doesn't speak
the rest of the
ride. Then we pull
up to the base.
I lean forward to
pay the driver, and
the driver says in
perfect English with an
American accent, Thank you,
ma'am. Turns out he
lived in Chicago for
ten years. He looks
at me and goes,
I know it wasn't
you. I wanted to
disappear. At the restaurant,
he starts yelling at
me because I called
the Air Force guys
pretty boys. He orders
me a margarita I
didn't want, then orders
himself two appetizers, beers,
and a steak. He
snaps at the server,
sends his food back,
just everything. Then the
check comes. He says,
oh, we'll split it
right down the middle.
So I grabbed that
check and said, oh,
if we're splitting it,
let's split it. These
beers are yours. The
steak is yours. The
appetizers are yours. The
margarita was technically mine
even though you drank
it. But I'll take
that and my salad,
and you, sir, can
pay for the rest.
He opens his mouth
and I snap. What?
Did I miss something?
He was silent the
entire ride back, which
of course I paid
for. I told his
supervisor how it went.
Next morning at PT,
he showed up in
the wrong uniform. Got
smoked pretty severely, I
heard. We never spoke
again.