So I matched with
this guy on Tinder.
He seemed cultured, talked
about great authors, literature,
art. I was actually
impressed. First date was
fine, kind of. He
apologized for not kissing
me. Said he'd been
told he's a bad
kisser and that girls
dump him over it.
He also accidentally said,
I love you. Out
loud. On the first
date. Red flags everywhere,
but I gave him
a second chance anyway.
We went to a
museum. And in the
car on the way
there, he was a
completely different person. Obnoxiously
loud music. Wouldn't talk
to me. Kept saying
reading was a waste
of time. Then, at
the museum, he kept
rubbing himself on me
while I was literally
just trying to look
at the art. When
he leaned in to
kiss me again, he
soaked my entire face.
I finally told him,
hey, I don't think
this is working. He
stood up from the
bench and he started
screaming in the middle
of a public museum
about how he was
a great kisser and
had a big D
and that I just,
quote, didn't get it.
I ran out of
there so fast.