This is Dating Horror
Story, Episode 7. So,
I matched with this
girl on Bumble. We
had a great text
exchange, we both like
Star Wars, hiking, real
conversations. She suggested coffee.
I said yes. I
show up at the
coffee shop. She's there,
smiling, with a clipboard.
I sit down. Before
I can even order,
she opens this clipboard
and pulls out a
printed list. Laminated. Each
row has a checkbox.
The header says, quote,
candidate pre-screening round one.
No joke. She goes,
don't worry. This is
just my screening process.
I do this for
every date. The questions,
salary range, degree level,
religious affiliation, why your
most recent relationship ended.
whether you want children,
and by what year.
Each answer, she literally
checks a box with
a pen, on a
clipboard, in a coffee
shop, while I sip
a latte. After 15
minutes, she goes, quote,
Okay, you're at 7
out of 12. You
need 9 to advance
to round 2. She
pulls out a second
page labeled round 2
questions. I told her
I had to use
the bathroom. There was
a back exit. I
left. Three hours later,
she texts. Most candidates
run. That's why I
prepped round two questions
early.