So I matched with
this guy on Tinder.
We'd been chatting for
a few days, everything
seemed great. We had
a lot in common,
his pictures were cute,
he lived close by.
I invited him over
to grill some burgers.
He asked if he
could bring anything. I
said, sure, bring some
bacon for the burgers.
He agreed and said
he'd be over soon.
Fifteen minutes go by,
then thirty. Then he
texts me. I've driven
by a couple times
and chickened out. Are
you sure you want
me to come over?
Maybe a red flag,
but I figured he
was just nervous. I
told him to come
on, I'm hungry. So
this Hagrid-looking guy shows
up, much different than
his Cedric picture. That's
all right, I can
move past that. But
from the minute he
walked up, he did
not take a breath.
Within five minutes, I
knew his entire life
story. From his aunt,
who hated their grandma,
to his father who
collects taxidermy. I put
the burgers on. When
they're ready, he pulls
out a Ziploc bag
from his pocket, with
two pieces of bacon
in it. He puts
them only on his
burger. We sit down
to eat. I finished
my burger before he
even started his, because
he did not stop
talking the entire time.
Then he reaches into
his pocket and pulls
out a vial, about
two inches tall with
a cork in it,
filled with a grayish
powder. He must have
noticed me staring at
it. He said, Oh,
all super casual. I'd
like to introduce you
to my mother. I
just stared at him.
I didn't know whether
to laugh or cry
or run. He tells
me I like to
bring her to any
important event in my
life. She also has
ashes in this necklace
and in this ring
and this half sleeve
tattoo is for her.
Now look, I've lost
people close to me.
I do not judge
anyone for how they
grieve. But this man
brought a V-I-A-L of
his mother's ashes, set
them on the table
for our first date.
He finished his burger.
I made some excuse
about having to clock
in for work at
9.30pm. He texted me
before he even got
to his car. My
mother really liked you.
I can't wait to
see you again. I
told him I didn't
feel the connection. To
him or his mother.