This is Dating Horror
Story Episode 4. So,
I was in a
five-year relationship. It ended
earlier this year. I'd
been single, just rebuilding
myself. Halloween. Friday night.
No plans. I was
lonely and bored, so
I downloaded Hinge for
the first time ever.
Within one day, I
had over a hundred
likes. Overwhelming. A few
guys asked me out
within two days. One
of them seemed actually
attractive. And he lived
in my town. So
I said yes. Date.
The very next day.
Red flag number one,
he insisted on picking
me up. Like really
insisted. Quote, I'm a
true gentleman. I told
him I'd just meet
him there. He doubled
down. I doubled down
harder. He gave up.
I get to the
restaurant. Nice place. His
pick. On the pricey
side. He's already there.
He's already ordered drinks
for both of us,
before I even sat
down. Already weird. But
I roll with it.
We talk about jobs.
What we want in
life. He gets all
vulnerable. Says he wants
real love. Says he
feels something different about
me. Versus other women.
Skeptical? Of course. But
I let it ride.
An hour in, he
orders another drink, plus
two appetizers, plus an
entree. I just got
my entree. He keeps
pushing a second drink
on me. I don't
drink that much. He
drinks it himself. Then
he says, and this
is the line quote,
I had so much
to drink. I have
to use the bathroom.
I'm sitting there, alone,
and the little voice
in my head goes,
oh, oh no. Five
minutes, 10, 15. The
waitress comes by. I'm
holding back tears because
I know I tell
her I'm on a
first date and I
think he just left.
She gets the manager.
He left me with
the bill. He left.
On Halloween. After ordering
enough food for three
people and giving me
the whole true gentleman
performance, the manager felt
so bad. They split
the check to just
my entree. So, that
was my first date
in six years. I
am never doing this
again.