This is Dating Horror
Story, Episode 5. So
I matched with this
girl on Bumble. We
talked for a week.
Seemed great. She asks
if she can bring
a friend to the
date. I say sure,
no big deal. I
show up. I walk
over and introduce myself
to who I think
is my date. The
girl from her profile.
She gets confused, looks
at me weird, and
then points behind her
to her friend, who's
just casually waving at
me. I'm very confused."
After a dizzying back
and forth, I finally
ask, Is this a
prank? They get confused
and annoyed. So I
pull out Bumble, show
the girl I thought
was my date her
own face on someone
else's profile. She is
pissed. And that's when
it finally clicked in
the catfisher's brain that
bringing the person whose
photos you stole to
the date was maybe,
maybe a bad idea.
They start arguing. Catfisher
plays victim. The friend
tries to make logical
sense of it all.
I'm just sitting there,
spinning a paper straw
like a fidget spinner,
completely silent. I quietly
excused myself to the
bathroom, took my time,
read some articles, took
a poop, Why not?
When I came back,
the pretty friend was
still there to apologize
on behalf of her
disaster of a friend.
I figured, what the
heck? I asked if
she wanted to grab
a real date. She
said I seemed like
a great guy, but
she has a boyfriend.
We parted ways. I
went and bought myself
sushi. Reparations for the
chaos. Don't catfish. It
never works out.