This is Dating Horror
Story, Episode 6. So,
I'm on Bumble, and
one of my prompts
on the app is
about why I bake.
Specifically, Tress Lech's cake.
Different flavors. It's kind
of my thing. This
girl matches with me.
She specifically comments on
the baking thing. I'm
thinking, bingo. I have
an in. So I
suggest a baking exchange.
We pick a date.
We pick a time.
We're locked in. The
day arrives. I'm in
the kitchen. Carrot cake
tres leches. I'm putting
in work. Flour. Eggs.
Three kinds of milk.
Hours of prep. The
whole production. Cake is
done. It's gorgeous. I
want to send her
a photo, just like
surprise. Look what I
made. Unmatched. One hour
before our scheduled meetup.
Just gone. I'm standing
in my kitchen. Apron
on. with this beautiful
carrot cake tres leches
that nobody is going
to eat with me.
And I now have
to wash every single
dish alone. I just
wanted a cute girl
to eat my food.
Now I'm just depressed,
eating cake by myself,
like I'm in a
Hallmark movie about loneliness.